&gt；&gt；steve kinney：那么，你告诉我所有的层，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So,
you told me all layers,
你告诉我对他们没有影响。
you told me I have no impact on them.
这真的很令人沮丧，你可以向浏览器提出建议。
That was really demoralizing,
you can make suggestions to the browser.
它有它的规则，它做它的事情，对，你可以说，
It has its rules, it does its thing,
right, you can say,
嘿，你会考虑把这层变成自己的一层吗？
hey, would you consider
making this its own layer?
对，他们就像，一切都会改变，我只是告诉你。
Right, and they're like,
it's gonna change, I'm just telling you.
一切都会改变，你不会想要重新粉刷，浏览器，
Things are gonna change, you're not gonna
wanna do all that repainting, browser,
我告诉你，对吧？
I'm telling you, right?
您可以说服浏览器并建议它成为自己的层。
You can convince the browser and
recommend that it become its own layer.
因此它的工作方式是一个称为will-change的CSS属性。
And so the way it works is a CSS
property called will-change.
然后无论你认为什么属性都会改变。
And then whatever property
you think is going to change.
我们的很多例子都是侧边栏，我们做了转换。
And a lot of our examples are sidebar,
we did with the transform.
我有，每次我用这个，我觉得它需要太多的争论。
I have, every time I've used this,
I think it takes so much arguments.
每次我使用这个，我一直在使用Transform。
Every time I've used this one,
I'm using transform all the time.
所以这就是我用的例子，
So that's gonna be the example that I use,
因为我想不出另一个好理由。
cuz I couldn't come up with
a good reason for another one.
好吧，这个人的支持率是多少？
All right, what's the support for
this one look like?
IE和Edge不支持它，你会觉得，好吧，他们落后了。
IE and Edge don't support it, and you'll
be like, well, they are lagging behind.
实际上，Edge认为他们的合成原因是这样的
Actually, Edge is of the opinion that
their compositing reasons are so
幸好他们不需要你的建议，对吧？
good that they don't need
your suggestions, right?
[笑]他们并没有落后
[LAUGH] It's not like they're behind,
这对可能提出我过于简单化的情况的人是不公平的。
that's not fair to whoever probably made
that case that I oversimplify like that.
但我们是朋友，这很酷[笑]。
But we're amongst friends,
it's cool [LAUGH].
他们不相信这是必要的，所以他们没有实施它的意图。
They don't believe it's necessary, so
they have no intent on implementing it.
好的部分是，这是一个渐进的增强。
And the nice part is,
this is a progressive enhancement.
这不是说，嗯，我不能使用它，因为我支持IE或Edge，
It's not like, well,
I can't use it cuz I support IE or Edge,
那它就什么都不做了。
it just doesn't do anything then.
[笑]对，没关系，它不会破坏网页，
[LAUGH] Right, it's fine,
it doesn't break the web page,
它没有做错任何事情，在这种情况下，它只是一个无操作。
it doesn't do anything wrong,
it's just a no-op in that case.
然后是Opera Mini，它将你的网页呈现为图像
And then Opera Mini,
it renders your web page as an image and
将其发送到电话，因此它不做任何事情。
sends it to the phone, so
it doesn't do anything.
每次你看到其中一个我可以使用图表，Opera Mini总是红色的。
Every time you see one of these can I
use charts, Opera Mini is always red.
但除此之外，它在其他浏览器上都有很好的支持。
But other than that, it's got pretty good
support across the rest of the browsers.
就像我说的，当它什么都不做的时候，
And like I said,
when it doesn't do anything,
这也很好，因为它什么都不做，不会断裂。
that is also fine cuz then it just
doesn't do anything, it doesn't break.
您可以使用它，并且支持它的浏览器将支持它，
You can use it and
browsers that support it will support it,
浏览器不会，不会。
browsers that don't, don't.
对此有一种古老的方法，就是translateZ。
There was an old hack for
this, which is translateZ.
其是改变元素的3D定位。
Which is to change the 3D
positioning of an element.
你可以看到，我们将它设置为0，这将使它成为自己的层，但是
And you can see, we're setting it to 0,
this will make it its own layer, but
它会强迫它。
it will force it.
Will-Change会更好一点，因为你会提出这样的建议，
will-change is a little bit better because
you make the recommendation saying,
这可能会成为它自己的一层，我只是告诉你。
this may become its own layer,
I'm just telling you.
以前，你就像，那是它自己的一层，做吧，然后
Before, you were like,
that's its own layer, do it, and
你已经欺骗了浏览器来做这件事。
you've tricked the browser into doing it.
你有这种信任关系，但你违反了它，所以这不是很好。
You have this relationship of trust and
you violated it, so that's not great.
所以一般来说，这是一个黑客，这是一种黑客，但是
So generally speaking, this is a hack,
this is kind of a hack, but
这是一个记录的，支持的，推荐的黑客攻击，所以它很好。
it's a documented, supported,
recommended hack, so it's fine.
酷，所以我要做的是，
Cool, so what I'm gonna do is,
我要取下这个页面的非视网膜版本，然后
I'm gonna take that non-retina
version of the page, and
给它Will-Change的CSS属性，我们就会看到它有什么影响。
give it the CSS property of will-change,
and we'll see what effect that has.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：所以如果我在这里进入，这个被调用并转到style.css。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So if I go in here into,
this one's called and go to style.css.
我要告诉标题，&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
I'm gonna tell the header,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
我要告诉脚注同样的事情。
I'm gonna tell the footer the same thing.
我会回去，&gt；&gt；steve kinney：然后
And I will go back,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
不会再重新粉刷了。
no more repaints.
非常酷，所以它起作用了，就像我说的，你得到它是为了
Very cool, and so it works,
like I said, you got it for
如果您使用读取到屏幕，则免费，因为浏览器已对此进行了优化
free if you're using read to screen, cuz
the browser has made that optimization for
你，我没有它，现在它存在了。
you, I didn't have it, and now it exists.
我们将在一秒钟内看一个稍微直观的示例，但是
We're gonna look at a slightly more
intuitive example in a second, but
我们回去吧。
let's go back.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：这是我做出改变之前的图层，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So here were
the layers before I made that change,
下面是后面的几层。
here were the layers after.
让我们把这些幻灯片再做两遍，前，后，前，
Let's do those slides two more times,
before, after, before,
之后，对吧，明白重点了吗？
after, right, get the major point?
现在，当我们滚动页面时，底层正在移动。
Now, when we scroll the page,
that underlying layer is moving.
合成器基本上只是移动它，但不是重新绘制它。
The compositor is basically just
moving it, but it's not repainting it.
我们没必要说，嘿，
We don't have to be like, hey,
你现在的样子和你在这张幻灯片里有多少人在一起？
what you look like now with how
much of you's in this slide?
我们只需在页眉和页脚下面上下滑动，
We simply slide it up and
down underneath the header and the footer,
也不会改变。
which also aren't changing.
工作越少，工作越快。
And that's less work, less work is faster.
我们要跳过绘画，我们要跳过布局，
We got to skip painting,
we got to skip layout,
我们直接去了合成器，这很好。
we went directly to compositor,
which is great.
所以，是的，把所有的东西都做成一层，对吧，看起来很棒，把所有的东西都分层。
So yeah, make everything a layer, right,
seems great, layer all the things.
层本身并不是免费的，这又是一组权衡。
Layers themselves aren't free, and
it's, again, a set of trade-offs.
因此，为了浏览器的利益，管理层需要做一定的工作。
So managing layers takes a certain
amount of work on the browser's behalf.
每一层都需要保存在主服务器和主服务器之间的共享内存中
Each layer needs to be kept in
shared memory between the main and
复合螺纹。
composite threads.
当它比绘画快的时候，这是很好的，但是如果你继续
When it's faster than painting,
it's great, but if you go ahead and
你把一切都变成了一层，[笑]。
you make everything a layer, [LAUGH].
如果一切都是一层，那么你就有了这整件事，
If everything is a layer,
then you have this entire thing,
你必须把所有这些都留在记忆里。
you have to keep all of that in memory.
它试图在引擎盖下帮助你，这就像放在括号里
It's trying to help you out under
the hood, this is like putting parentheses
尝试在JavaScript中帮助解析器，对吗？
around everything to try to like help
the parser in JavaScript, right?
如果你选择退出它有用的算法，你就有效地使它毫无用处。
If you opt out of its helpful algorithms,
you've effectively made it useless.
如果一切都要优化，你猜怎么着，没有什么是优化的。
If everything should be optimized,
guess what, nothing is optimized.
我们现在的例子有一个问题，对吧？
And our current example has a problem,
right?
我告诉过你，那些被自动转化的东西会自动得到它们自己的层，对吧？
I told you, things that are transformed
automatically get their own layer, right?
定位在视网膜上的东西会有自己的一层。
Things that are position fixed
on retina get their own layer.
而且，这看起来很奇怪，它被称为意志-改变，但是
Also, it seems weird that
it's called will-change, but
它并没有真正改变什么，对吧？
it didn't really change anything, right?
似乎我一直在对你隐瞒一些事情。
Seems like I've kind of hiding
something from you this entire time.
也就是说，CSS规则非常适合了解，
Which is,
the CSS rules are great for knowing,
浏览器擅长找出自己层的东西。
the browser's good at figuring out
something that is its own layer.
真正有用的是弄清楚，等等，
What will-change is really useful for
is figuring out, wait,
它以前不是自己的层，也不应该是自己的层。
it wasn't its own layer before, and
shouldn't have been its own layer.
但可能很快就需要成为它自己的一层，对吧？
But might need to be its own
layer very shortly, right?
因此，我们再次呈现页面，但随后JavaScript出现并
So again, we render the page,
but then JavaScript shows up and
就像，我要改变一切，对吗？
it's like,
I'm gonna change everything, right?
所以我们知道，嘿，这个盒子，这就是我们要用的例子。
So we know, hey, this box,
that's the example we're gonna use.
但是页面上的这个元素，它是静态的，
But this element on the page,
it was static,
但是用户将要做一些事情。
but the user's about to do something.
我要把它做成CSS transs，我很快就会改变它的样式，对吧，
I am going to make it a CSS trans, I'm
gonna change the styles on it soon, right,
你有两个选择，浏览器。
you have two choices, browser.
无论是A，你都可以在我问你的时候弄清楚所有这些层的东西
Either A, you can figure out all this
layer stuff at the moment I'm asking you
做些事情，或者你可以做好准备，对吧？
to do stuff, or you can get ready, right?
我要告诉你，这个盒子会变，这个元素会变。
I'm gonna tell you that this box is gonna
change, this element is gonna change.
它还没有改变，但是你为什么不，当你什么都不做的时候，
It's not changing yet, but why don't you,
while you're not doing anything else,
提升它到自己的层，所以当它开始的时候，你准备好了吗？
promote it to its own layer, so
when it's time to get going, you're ready?
对，所以这是一个不是很有帮助的例子，对吧。
Right, so this is an example where
it's not super helpful, right.
在这种情况下，我们已经在改造这个侧边栏，所以它已经是它自己的层了。
We're already transforming this sidebar in
this case, so it's already its own layer.
但可能更有用的是说，好吧，
But what might become more
useful is to say, all right,
想象一下顶层的意志-改变不在那里[笑]所以。
imagine that top will-change
isn't up there [LAUGH] so.
&GT；&GT；史蒂夫·金尼：我们将有一个过渡，当他们盘旋时，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: We'll have a transition,
when they hover,
我们知道他们会点击，对吧？
we know that they're gonna click, right?
当他们点击时，我们会添加开放的东西，对吗？
When they click,
we're gonna add the open thing, right?
理论上，只要他们一点击，我们就可以将其提升到自己的层。
We could theoretically promote it to
its own layer as soon as they click.
但当它们盘旋时，很可能会点击，对吧，所以
But when they hover, It's likely that
they're going to click, right, so
这时我们将添加转换，并且我们确实需要在之后清理它。
that's when we'll add the transform, and
we do need to clean it up afterwards.
我们将添加变换，然后它将被提升到它自己的层。
We'll add the transform,
then it'll be promoted to it's own layer.
当他们开始点击时，只需将该层滑过即可。
By the time they get around to clicking,
just slide that layer over.
对，这是一种非常有用的方式。
Right, it's a really
useful way of doing it.